All right, Jim.
Anything else you want to make sure to mention?
I think, again, the thing to really know is that
if you accept the premise that we've talked about here today,
which is that this is a choice everybody has to make and
it's about skills, then a really important thing to
do is to set specific goals.
And I guess one thing we haven't talked about is the reason I think
people often don't engage in courage at work is they think of
the very scariest thing that comes to mind first,
and then they, rightfully so, conclude one of two things.
I'm not going to do that because it's too difficult, and
it'll go terribly
or they'll say, I tried it,
and because it was so incredibly difficult and I wasn't ready,
I totally screwed it up,
and that only confirmed for me how stupid choosing courage is.
I think this is a kin to the idea that you're not a runner,
but you decide you're going to run a ten K.
Well, the dumbest thing to do would be to go out and try to
run ten K the first day.
Right.
and because of so many injuries,
you probably never jog again.
So what I encourage people to do is build a personal
courage ladder.
Yeah, you can put that scariest thing on the top rung,
but put some sort of moderately difficult things on the middle
rungs and put some things that,
you know, you're a little afraid of but you could imagine doing on
the lowest rungs and then choose those to start with.
Because as with any skill, the way you actually build
competence over time is you start small and you have a little
success and you feel better about yourself, it increases your
motivation.
So what we haven't really, I think talked about enough is the
importance of starting small.
That's how all skills are developed.